(Mrs Davis:)You're sweet.
(Mrs Davis:)-Good night, Dr. Koothrappali.
-Good night.
(Howard:)Looks like she accepted your apology.
And than some.
I think we had a moment.
(Howard:)Please, you did not
have a moment.
(Raj:)Who died and made you
king of moments?
(Raj:)Okay, fine.
Let's say there was a moment.
(Howard:)-There was.
-There wasn't. But...
(Howard:)But even if there was,
what are you gonna do about it?
(Raj:)I will slowly seduce her
until she falls helpless into my bed,
(Raj:)hungry for the pleasure
only I can give her.
(Howard:)-So nothing.
-No, not a thing.
(Penny(acting):)I'm so glad the police
finally caught
(Penny(acting):)that psychotic
genetically-engineered ape.
That is my girlfriend!
I swear to God!
(Everyone(on ship):)Leonard! Leonard!
Leonard! Leonard!